Now the situation has changed again.
Notice how there are two bodies that can be seen.
Where are you?
Where is the center of awareness?
No need to decide, just notice.
I would like you to move parts of your body and to observe.
As before, please raise your right hand and make small, regular movements, up and down, right and left, slowly.
Notice the movements of the body.
Now place your right hand on your left shoulder.
Observe.
Now place your left hand on your right shoulder.
Notice the movements of the body.
Now move your right hand to your lap and then move your left hand to your lap.
Rest like this for a moment.
Where are you?
At the location of the body you see?
At the location from where you see?
Somewhere else?
Just notice and stay in this state.